notgoingtouni.co.uk 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy

**_Not going to uni (Ngtu) Privacy Statement_**  
[www.notgoingtouni.co.uk](http://www.notgoingtouni.co.uk/) & [www.notgoingtouni.com](http://www.notgoingtouni.com/)  are owned and run by not going to uni Ltd.

**Introduction**

At Ngtu we are sensitive to privacy issues on the internet. We believe that it is important you know how we treat the information about you, which we receive from you. To this end we have created the following privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy on the internet and especially within the use of this website.

**General Privacy Statement**

In general you can visit Ngtu without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about you. Our servers automatically collect domain names, IP addresses, browser details, your country of origin and how you got to the site (via the use of cookies and server generated technology – please see the section 'What are cookies' for more information). This information is aggregated to measure things such as the number of visits, time spent on the site, pages viewed etc. Ngtu uses this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the service we offer to you. Personally identifiable information such as email address, home address, first and last names, and other such identifiable information is only known when voluntarily provided by a visitor for the purpose of registration, or in communication with other members and guests.

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post personal information to discussion forums, wikis, Journals, Blogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.  
Personally identifiable information that is collected in response to the use of this site is retained by Ngtu, and only used in the improvement of services and in contact from us, to the user. We do not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose this information outside this company, except:

  * where disclosure is required by law or;

-    when the visitor chooses to "apply" to an opportunity, advert or similar.

        -   From time to time, Ngtu may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on Ngtu. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmission to our site; any transmission is at you own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use the strict procedures to try and prevent unauthorised access.

It is your responsibility to keep your site login information secure when it's in your possession. If you are using a shared computer, please ensure you log out of Ngtu or close down the browser before leaving the computer for the next user.

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such Websites.

**What is a cookie?**

The information supplied by a cookie can help us provide you with a better online experience and assist us in the profile of our visitors. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows. You have the option to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these means that personalised services cannot be provided to that user and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of Ngtu's features. For more information on cookies please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**How we use IP addresses**

To help us maintain a safe website your IP address maybe displayed alongside your posts, and can be used to investigate illegal/inappropriate user behaviour. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose any problems with our server or to administer Ngtu. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information that helps us understand our users requirements.

**Security**

Ngtu has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under its control. Please try and keep your log in information (username and/or password) secure at all times. If you suspect that the security of your login information has been breached you can email [info@notgoingtouni.co.uk](mailto:info@notgoingtouni.co.uk)

**Children**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Ngtu is intended for general use and does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on persons under 12 years-of-age. As no part of Ngtu is directed to persons under 12 we would suggest you use other websites more suited to your age group. If Ngtu learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 12-years-of-age has been collected on Ngtu, then Ngtu will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 12 has obtained access to Ngtu or has created a membership account, then you may alert Ngtu at [info@notgoingtouni.co.uk](mailto:info@notgoingtouni.co.uk) and request that Ngtu delete that child's personal information from its systems.

Parents and legal guardian's should supervise the online activities of their children, and should consider the use of parental control tools available from online services and software providers that help provide a child-friendly Internet environment.

**Viewing and correcting your personal information**

In the majority of cases, Ngtu will allow you to view any information that is held about you if you ask for it either in an email or in writing. If you then inform us that part or all of the information is incorrect, we will review it. If we also believe that it is incorrect, we will then correct our records.

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your rights of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of up to £10.00 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**Third Party Advertisements**

Any advertisement appearing on this website (including but not limited to banners, text adverts, skyscrapers, emails, private messages etc) is delivered to you by us, or on our behalf by our web advertising partners.

Information you provide us with may be used anonymously to ensure that you receive more targeted advertisements, but no personal information that you provide us with will ever be passed to a third party.  
Anonymous aggregated information based on users' activities e.g. number of people clicking on an advert will be passed to advertisers. No information about specific users activity will ever be passed to a third party.

**Changes and updates to this privacy statement**

This privacy statement from time to time may be revised without any further notice. We would advise you to revisit this page from time to time to keep up to date with any changes in the way we deal with information collected from you. Continued use of Ngtu constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any future amendments.

**Contacting Ngtu**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the conduct of Ngtu or your use of the service this website provides, you can contact:  
Administrator  
Not going to uni Ltd  
4a Oakwood Parade, Oakwood Hill, Loughton, Essex, IG10 3EL
